

PANUPONG SRISUPADECHA

FullstackDeveloper

CONTACTS

PHONE NUMBER

0902239879

EMAIL

ballyeah01@gmail.com

ADDRESS

379 group 7 bankok 24 road, khonkean city, 40000, Thailand

ABOUT ME

Hello, my name is Ball and I'm looking for a full stack developer job. I have experience in programming for about 5 years. I usually use laravel for development. Nowadays there are new technologies, so I can always study new languages. Currently, I'm a freelancer with work. For example, create an online table reservation system. Store owners can design their own store layouts using REACTJS, EXPRESSJS to develop the PHP LARAVEL postal system. Reference works:

https://www.youtube.com/watch? v=CRKDOvCW3i0,

https://www.jongtable

.com/replayground and many other works

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULLSTACKDEVELOPER

Bangkok

2fellow

Jan 2016 - Nov 2016

Make a GPS tracking system for transporting goods using the Google Maps API, using php jquery for development.

FULLSTACKDEVELOPER

♀ Khonkaen

DAMASCA

Jan 2017 - Jan 2019

Create a data storage system and issue statistical reports. Liver leaf cancer patient information using php laravel for development

FRONTENDDEVELOPER

♥ Khonkaen

Dekdam co.,ltd Jan 2019 - Dec 2019

Acting as a frontend developer, designing ux/ui appearances, developing e-learning systems, using angularis mainly for development.

FULLSTACKDEVELOPER

freelance

Jan 2020 - Oct 2023

- · POS system regarding postal transportation system
- · Online restaurant reservation system
- e-office system
- Online resume creation system
- · Flutter application captures sms

EDUCATION

2012

BACHELOR

Khonkaen University , khonkaen

Faculty: Computer Science

Major: Information Communication and Technology

2008

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Khonkaenwittayoyon, khonkaen

SKILLS

Html,Css

REACT IS NEXT IS

ANGULARJS

VUEJS

GOLANG

PHP,LARAVEL

MySQL,Postgresql

Ubuntu, Nginx, Cloudflare